JASON CRABTREE, Full Stack Developer based in Auckland, New Zealand

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Full Stack Developer with 3 years of professional experience building front-end applications, APIs, and CMS websites seeking opportunities building Full Stack Web Apps with React & TypeScript

TECHNOLOGIES and LANGUAGES

• Languages: JavaScript, TypeScript, React, HTML, CSS, GraphQL, HubL, NodeJS

• Technologies: Git, CI/CD, AWS Lambda, API Design, Tailwind, CSS-in-JS, Design Systems

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Front End Developer, Hype & Dexter, Auckland, NZ

May 2021 - Present

Built and deployed dynamic web applications and websites for business clients in NZ & Australia with the HubSpot CRM & CMS platform. Built 2 custom CRM extensions for HubSpot using React

- Built a React App using HubSpot's extension system and Google Autocomplete APIs to search
 for address details and populate React Hooks and a user-editable form. Upon user
 confirmation, the form uses an AWS Lambda API function to update data in the CRM database
- Built 4 front-end web applications using JavaScript, TypeScript, serverless APIs, GraphQL,
 HTML & CSS. Each application displayed dynamic, filtered data fetched from the client's unique HubSpot database via API, restricted access based on user authentication, and provided secure APIs to create, read, update and delete data inside HubSpot's CRM database
- Built 8 CMS-based websites as Lead Developer, and contributed to 4 other websites in a team
 of 4 developers. Live Projects: Comms Council, Integration Glue, Australian Water Association,
 CGProperty, Ozwater, ClearPoint, DBVisit, Figured, Eftpos NZ, Coronation, EnergySmart
- Built a new project template v1, used for all future web projects (~25+) by a 5-developer team

International travel & online education courses

Feb 2019 - April 2021

IAG (Insurance Australia Group), Auckland, NZ

Oct 2014 - Jan 2019

- Customer Experience Design Lead 11 months
- Customer Insights Consultant 1 year
- Senior Insurance Claims Manager 8 months
- Insurance Claims Manager 2 years

Emergency Call Handler, St John Ambulance, Auckland, NZ

Sept 2012 - Aug 2014

SKILLS AND ACCOMPLISHMENTS

- Strong problem-solving capabilities able to break problems down into achievable tasks
- Effective at communicating technical and business needs with colleagues and stakeholders
- Received multiple peer awards for innovation, teamwork and leadership (Hype & Dexter, IAG)

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Arts (B.A.), Psychology Feb 2009 - July 2012 Massey University, New Zealand

027-322-4961 • jasontcrabtree@gmail.com • jasontcrabtree.com • github.com/jasontcrabtree